扰乱他们  让他们无法安心做事
Unsettle 'em. Throw 'em off their game.
买下他们想要
Buy up the price on names
加仓的全部股票
they want to increase their size in.
耗尽他们的优势
Costing them upside
并给他们的利润造成微小的损失
and picking tiny little percentages off their profits.
就像古老的水刑
It'll be like the old water torture...
一滴  一滴  一滴
Drip, drip, drip.
就像二战时日本人做的那样
Like the Japanese in W.W.II.
虽然水刑是中国人发明的
Even though the Chinese invented it...
那不是中国人发明的
No they didn't...
那它为什么叫做"中国式水刑"
Then why is it called 'Chinese Water Torture?'
泰勒会忽略这种损失
Taylor will try to ignore it.
安慰自己那只是些偶尔的小失误
Tell themselves that it's just a few bips here or there.
-但这行不通  -他们对数理完美性的要求
- But it won't work. - Their need for mathematical perfection
会侵蚀自己的利益
will erode their well-being.